My relationship with sport is one of absolute contempt.
I think sport is crap.
One day, for whatever reason, I was a creative person,
I was...
lively.
Hahahahaha!
And then, a teacher gave us a test
and asked us to leave the test when time was up
and he was going to collect it.
So I, with my arms crossed,
put the exam on my head.
Hahahahaha!
I made his job easier, from my point of view.
He was coming from behind,
and I, well, with my arms crossed,
I made it easier for him, from my point of view.
He was coming from behind.
Well, so, what did this guy do, who I hope is watching me?
He left the exams
and slapped me from behind.
Hahahahaha!
But a slap that, like cartoons,
left the exam in the air and me on the ground.
Hahahahaha!
Pepe, when did you first discover
that your family wasn't rich?
Right after killing them.
Who thought it was so urgent to carry a nail clipper around
to add a keychain function to it?
Hahahahaha!
I would propose that person as president of the government.
Because we are seeing that anyone is suitable.
Hahahahahaha!
I am always the one who starts the conga line at weddings.
I always like it, I grab, you know?
The typical aunt, grandmother, single, older,
who is a bag of bones.
I always grab her and lift her a little.
Then, everyone believes...
Everyone believes that she leads us,
but, in addition, as they are...
Hahahahaha!
As they are fibrous, I move her like this and she moves her arms.
So, I got so carried away that once I did it, look,
at a funeral.
I'm not afraid because I'm...
drunken and adventurous,
but when I sleep I have no control over nightmares.
I'm terrified of falling asleep
and Bill Cosby sneaking into my bed at night.
Hahahahaha!
I believe dancing was invented by Stephen Hawking.
No, no.
Uh...
Damn, don't laugh that...
it almost cost him his life, look at how he ended up.
Hahahahaha!
What would you like to discover, Pepe?
Well, the obvious thing would be to say a vaccine against cancer, right?
But it's that...
cancer took my mother-in-law, I am very grateful to cancer.
Hahahahaha!
I once went to the zarzuela racetrack
to see what horse racing was like.
In the first race there was a horse named Newman.
And I remembered the postman from Seinfeld.
And I bet on Newman. And he won the race.
I won 5 euros with 40 cents because my bet had been miserable.
Hahahahaha!
Then I went to the next race and a horse named Joy Division ran.
And I bet everything I had and he came last.
Hahahahaha!
What have I learned? Nothing!
Hahahahahaha!
I know that many people who hear this will think that I am heartless,
but I have masturbated behind my girlfriend's back.
Hahahahaha!
I don’t mean on her behind while she was sleeping, although also.
I mean, if she's in the room next door,
I've masturbated thinking about other women.
Hahahahaha!
I want to come out here with a catheter and in diapers.
And unshaven.
But not because I'm very old, next week if possible.
Hahahahaha!
With the nightgown behind? Open from the back.
Do you have a date? A polka dot nightgown.
Do you have a date? A rectal examination.
Ah, you see! Of course! Hahahaha!
You only need to masturbate compulsively in case,
by chance, your ejaculation coincides,
wherever she is, with an orgasm from Monica Bellucci.
Once my girlfriend said, anal sex today.
Hahahahaha!
I said, come on, okay, I'm prepared.
And she took out a belt dildo worn by her.
Hahahahaha!
Strapon, it's called, right? Strapon.
Strapon.
Then she told me it was a seated prank,
but she saw me so enthusiastic that she put it in me bent.
I've masturbated thinking about me.
Hahahahaha!
But, beware, with greed, thinking about a threesome with two me's.
Ah, yes.
So, looking at it and suddenly realizing
and that, from a subjective point of view, my three selves are looking at me.
So I realized that there are four of us.
I'm tripping over your idyllic vision of school.
A place where you have to fucking get up early every day.
That, that.
Are you telling me that you, as a child,
with your 12 years, with your hairs or the eggs already,
going to class at nine was getting up early?
Sorry, Isabel.
Did you get up? Was going to class at nine getting up early?
Since you mention hairs and eggs,
I had a lot to do at night, okay?
Hahahahaha!
I propose a subject, also. Brown sciences.
There are the natural ones, which is very good, there are the social ones,
but brown sciences that teach you to get by
in difficult situations in life, right?